Finding Aid for the Tony Barrett Papers PASC.0061
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1. Television and motion picture scripts and production material
  - Treasury Men in Action (ABC, 1950-1951; NBC, 1951-1955)
    - THE CASE OF THE LEATHER BAG by Tony Barrett and Robert Sloane, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - THE CASE OF THE WHITE AGONY by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - THE CASE OF THE CUT-RATE WATCHES by Tony Barrett and Robert Sloane, 1955 (Box 80, Folder 16)
  - Union Pacific (Syndication, 1958-1959)
    - THE HAUNTED HILLS by Milton Geiger, 1957 July 18 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - THE DECISION by Tony Barrett, 1957 December 9 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - THE CHOICE by Tony Barrett from the story DYNAMITE by Milton Raison, undated (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - THE CHARMING RUSTLER by Gene Levitt, undated (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - WOMEN WITH GUNS, undated (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - THE WEDDING script pages, 1958 February 26 (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - THE TRESTLE by Tony Barrett, 1958 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - TO THE DEATH by Tony Barrett, 1958 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - THE ROAD-BLOCK by Tony Barrett, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - PRISON CAMP by Bill Barrett and Tony Barrett from a story by Biil Barrett, 1957 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - THE ROAD-BLOCK outlines and script pages by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Research material, undated (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - The Untouchables (ABC, 1959-1963)
    - THE SPOILER by Tony Barrett, 1963 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - THE HUNTING GROUND notes, undated (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - LINE OF FIRE by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - Wanted: Dead or Alive (CBS 1958-1961)
    - RICOCHET by Tony Barrett, 1958 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - THE LEGEND by Tony Barrett, 1959 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - RICOCHET outline by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 120, Folder 2)
- Series 2. Radio scripts and production material
  Most of the radio scripts represent acting roles for Tony Barrett. There are also several roles for Michael Ann Barrett. It is not clear what, if any, relationship exists between the two.
  - ABC Playhouse (ABC)
    - THE HUNTED by Milton Geiger from a story by Maurice Baudin Jr., 1953 April 13 (Box 102a, Folder 23)
  - The Adventures of Hashknife Hartley and Sleepy Stevens (Mutual, 1950-1951)
    - THE TENDERFOOT TRAIL by Gene Tuttle, 1951 August 27 (Box 111a, Folder 15)
    - HOLD-UP MAN IN BUFFALO GULCH by Ray Wilson, 1951 June 11 (Box 111a, Folder 16)
  - The Adventures of Philip Marlowe (NBC/CBS, 1947-1951)
    - THE YOUNG MAN'S FANCY, 1951 August 18 (Box 102a, Folder 19)
    - THE YOUNG MAN'S FANCY cast and crew sheet, 1951 August 16 (Box 107, Folder 20)
  - The Adventures of Sam Spade (ABC/CBS/NBC, 1946-1951)
    - Notes and script by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - THE SURE THING CAPER by John Michael Hayes, 1951 February 9 (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - THE SPANISH PRISONER CAPER, undated (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Barrie Craig, Confidential Investigator (NBC, 1951-1955)
    - Script pages, undated (Box 102a, Folder 12)
    - THE GOLDEN TOUCH by John Roeburt, 1955 February 10 (Box 107, Folder 12)
    - THE TEARLESS WIDOW by John Roeburt, 1954 October 20 (Box 107, Folder 13)
    - TWO DEAD MEN by John Roeburt, 1955 (Box 107, Folder 14)
  - Bold Venture (syndicated, 1951-1952)
    - #64 by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, undated (Box 107, Folder 15)
    - #43 by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, undated (Box 107, Folder 16)
    - #31 by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, undated (Box 107, Folder 17)
    - #10 by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, undated (Box 107, Folder 18)
    - GUNS BY NIGHT, undated (Box 107, Folder 19)
  - Broadway Is My Beat (CBS, 1949-1954)
    - Script, 1951 June 9 (Box 111a, Folder 1)
    - Script, 1950 June 9 (Box 111a, Folder 2)
    - Script by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1953 August 22 (Box 111a, Folder 3)
    - Script by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1953 February 14 (Box 111a, Folder 4)
    - THE CASE OF THE FRIENDLY CREDIT PICKPOCKET by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1952 March 22 (Box 111a, Folder 5)
    - Script by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1952 September 13 (Box 111a, Folder 6)
    - Script by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1952 October 4 (Box 111a, Folder 7)
    - Script by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1951 July 15 (Box 111a, Folder 8)
    - Script by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1953 January 3 (Box 111a, Folder 9)
    - Script by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1952 March 8 (Box 111a, Folder 10)
    - Script by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1951 October 13 (Box 111a, Folder 11)
    - Script by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1951 April 28 (Box 111a, Folder 12)
    - Script by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1952 June 9 (Box 111a, Folder 13)
    - #6 by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, undated (Box 111a, Folder 14)
  - Calling All Cars
    - Audition Script, undated (Box 106, Folder 8)
      This is the equivalent of a pilot script for a show produced by Gene Autry Enterprises.
  - Candy Matson (NBC radio, 1949-1951)
    - CANDY MATSON - YUKON 3-8309 by Natalie Masters, undated (Box 111, Folder 16)
  - Cathy and Elliott Lewis On Stage (CBS, 1953-1954)
    - VICKIE by Ross Murray and Anthony Barrett, 1953 October 25 (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - VICKIE by Ross Murray and Tony Barrett, undated (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - DRIFTWOOD, undated (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - THE FLING by Het Manheim and E. Jack Neuman, 1953 June 23 (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - CBS Radio Workshop (CBS, 1956-1957)
    - ANNIE CHRISTMAS by Edmund Brophy and Sam Pierce from a story by Edmund Brophy, 1956 October 7 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - The Cisco Kid (Don Lee-Mutual, 1946-1958)
    - PANCHO PLAYS POLO, 1953 November 17 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - THE DEVIL'S HIGHWAY, 1953 September 22 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - OUTLAW BRAND, 1953 June 9 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - STAGE TO SILVER CITY, 1953 May 12 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - THE LADY FROM LUBBOCK, 1953 January 10 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - ROSE OF RAYEN, 1952 November 11 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - OPERA IN ALBUQUERQUE, 1952 April 16 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - MORBID JONES AND THE BURIED GOLD, undated (Box 102, Folder 14)
  - The Clyde Beatty Show (Mutual, 1950-1952)
    - RHODESIAN RIDGEBACK, undated (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - CIRCUS TRAIN by Frank Hart Taussig and R.T. Smith, undated (Box 106, Folder 22)
    - AFRICAN MAHOUT by Frank Hart Taussig and R.T. Smith, undated (Box 106, Folder 23)
  - The Count of Monte Cristo (Mutual, 1946-1952)
    - THE WEEPING TREE, undated (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - THE HUNTSMAN'S VENGEANCE, undated (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - THE TOLTEC TITAN, undated (Box 105, Folder 20)
  - Dangerous Assignment (NBC, 1949-1953)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 111 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1952 July 14 (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 113 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1952 June 10 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 56 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1951 May 30 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 61 by Bob Ryf, 1951 July 24 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 63 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1951 August 7 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 66 by Bob Ryf, 1951 August 28 (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 69 by Bob Ryf, 1951 September 18 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 71 by Bob Ryf, 1951 October 2 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 76 by Bob Ryf, 1951 November 6 (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 72 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1951 October 9 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 99 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1952 March 31 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 103 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1952 May 8 (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 102 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1952 (Box 109, Folder 13)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 86 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1952 January 14 (Box 109, Folder 14)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 77 by Bob Ryf, 1951 November 13 (Box 109, Folder 15)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 46 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1951 (Box 109, Folder 16)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 53 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1951 (Box 109, Folder 17)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 98 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1952 March 27 (Box 109, Folder 18)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 58 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1951 (Box 109, Folder 19)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 89 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1952 January 31 (Box 109, Folder 20)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 59 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1951 (Box 109, Folder 21)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 70 by Bob Ryf, 1951 September 25 (Box 109, Folder 22)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE ___ by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1951 May 23 (Box 109, Folder 23)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 154 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1953 April 23 (Box 109, Folder 24)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 154, 1953 April 16 (Box 109, Folder 25)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 114 by Bob Ryf and Adrian Gendot, 1952 August 5 (Box 109, Folder 26)
    - Script, undated (Box 109, Folder 27)
    - Script pages, undated (Box 109, Folder 28)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 138, 1953 January 8 (Box 109a, Folder 1)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE ___, 1951 November 20 (Box 109a, Folder 2)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 133, 1952 November 26 (Box 109a, Folder 3)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 137, 1952 December 18 (Box 109a, Folder 4)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 145, 1953 February 19 (Box 109a, Folder 5)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 126, 1952 October 2 (Box 109a, Folder 6)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 125, 1952 September 26 (Box 109a, Folder 7)
    - LONDON outline by Tony Barrett, undated (Box 109a, Folder 8)
    - Script page, undated (Box 109a, Folder 9)
    - SERIES 2 EPISODE 54 title page, 1951 May 8 (Box 109a, Folder 10)
  - Defense Attorney (ABC, 1951-1952)
    - LADY OF THE LAW outline, undated (Box 88, Folder 20)
    - SCRIPT #20 by Joel Murcott, 1951 November 8 (Box 116a, Folder 1)
    - NO. 18 by Joel Murcott, 1951 October 25 (Box 116a, Folder 2)
    - NO. 17 by Joel Murcott, 1951 October 18 (Box 116a, Folder 3)
    - SCRIPT #15 by Joel Murcott, 1951 October 11 (Box 116a, Folder 4)
    - NO. 14 by Joel Murcott, 1951 October 4 (Box 116a, Folder 5)
    - SCRIPT #7 by Joel Murcott, 1951 August 17 (Box 116a, Folder 6)
    - SCRIPT #2 by Joel Murcott, 1951 July 13 (Box 116a, Folder 7)
    - #64, 1952 September 25 (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Series outline, undated (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - STANDBY #8 by Jack Speirs, undated (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - STANDBY #4 by Jack Speirs, 1951 November 14 (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - STANDBY #3 by Dwight Hauser, 1951 October 31 (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - STANDBY #2 by Joel Murcott, 1951 October 24 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - STANDBY #1 by Joel Murcott, 1951 October 1 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - NEW STANDBY #1, 1952 September 10 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - SERIES 3 SCRIPT #5, 1952 May 29 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - SERIES 3 #3 by Dwight Hauser, 1952 May 22 (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Script, 1951 November 1 (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Script, 1951 November 21 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - NEW STANDBY #1 by Tony Barrett, 1952 September 10 (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - #61 by Dwight Hauser, 1952 September 4 (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - #53 by Dwight Hauser, 1952 May 15 (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - #51 by Dwight Hauser, 1952 May 1 (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - #50 by Jack Speirs, 1952 April 24 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - #49 by Dwight Hauser, 1952 April 17 (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - #48 by Jack Speirs, 1952 April 10 (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - #29, 1951 December 20 (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - #28 by Joel Murcott, 1951 December 13 (Box 117, Folder 21)
    - #27 by Joel Murcott, 1951 December 6 (Box 117, Folder 22)
    - #26 by Joel Murcott, 1951 November 29 (Box 117, Folder 23)
    - #25 by Joel Murcott, 1951 November 21 (Box 117, Folder 24)
    - #24 by Joel Murcott, 1951 November 15 (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - Douglas of the World (Armed Forces Radio, 1952-1953)
    - THE GOLDEN TREASURE script pages, undated (Box 107, Folder 21)
  - Escape (CBS, 1947-1954)
    - THE KILLER MINE by Tony Ellis from a story by Hammond Innes, 1951 February 11 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - THE ABOMINABLE SNOWMAN by Anthony Ellis, 1953 September 13 (Box 110, Folder 3a)
    - THE BLUE HOTEL by E. Jack Neuman, 1953 May 24 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - THE FAR AWAY ISLAND by Charles Smith, 1953 June 21 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - ELEMENTALS by Meyer Dolinsky from a story by Stephen Vincent Benet, 1953 October 6 (Box 110, Folder 6)
    - TRANSPORT TO TERROR by Kathleen Hite, 1952 November 23 (Box 110, Folder 7)
    - INCIDENT IN QUITO by Ross Murray, 1952 December 7 (Box 110, Folder 8a)
    - CARNIVAL IN VIENNA by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, undated (Box 110, Folder 9)
    - BLOODBATH by James Poe, undated (Box 110, Folder 10)
    - NIGHTMARE IN THE SUN by Anthony Barrett, 1952 December 28 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - THE TARGET by Tony Barrett, 1954 September 18 (Box 110, Folder 12)
    - THE BOILING SEA title page, 1954 September 4 (Box 110, Folder 13)
    - BLOODWATERS by Anthony Barrett, undated (Box 110, Folder 14)
    - BLOODWATERS, undated (Box 110, Folders 15-16)
    - BLOODWATERS by Anthony Barrett, 1954 June 17 (Box 110, Folder 17)
  - Family Theater (Mutual, 1947-1957)
    - FLIGHT PLAN by Robert Hugh O'Sullivan, 1957 March 200 (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - The Freedom Story
    This series, whether produced or not, was an organ of James W. Fifield, Jr.
    - REMEDY FOR A SICK TOWN, 1951 October (Box 112, Folder 10)
    - THE MAFIA, 1951 September (Box 112, Folder 11)
  - Freedom USA (Syndicated, 1952)
    - THE HONEST LIE by Don Brinkley from a story by Robert Shaw, undated (Box 116a, Folder 8)
  - Gene Autry's Melody Ranch (CBS, 1940-1943, 1945-1956)
    - Script, 1951 September 15 (Box 107, Folder 9)
    - Script, 1953 June 13 (Box 107, Folder 10)
    - Script, 1953 September 10 (Box 107, Folder 11)
  - Gunsmoke (CBS, 1952-1961)
    - THE REED SURVIVES, 1955 June 11 (Box 106, Folder 13)
    - TAP DAY FOR KITTY by John Meston, 1955 July 23 (Box 106, Folder 14)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame (CBS, 1953-1955)
    - MARCUS WHITMAN, 1953 September 27 (Box 111, Folder 4)
  - Hollywood Sound Stage (1951-1952)
    - CALL NORTHSIDE 777, undated (Box 102a, Folder 17)
    - THE OX-BOW INCIDENT, undated (Box 102a, Folder 22)
  - Hollywood Star Playhouse (CBS/ABC/NBC, 1950-1953)
    - THE PROFESSOR STAYS HOME by Frank and Doris Hursley, 1951 September 27 (Box 106, Folder 18)
    - THE SITTING DUCK by Anthony Barrett, 1952 October 12 (Box 113, Folder 1)
    - STEP RIGHT UP AND DIE by Anthony Barrett, undated (Box 113, Folder 2)
    - OUTPOST by Joel Murcott, 1950 September 4 (Box 113, Folder 3)
    - Script for Anne Baxter, 1950 September 18 (Box 113, Folder 4)
    - HARRY BROCKTON'S WIFE by Frank Burt, 1953 February 8 (Box 113, Folder 5)
    - TIME TO KILL, undated (Box 113, Folder 6)
    - Script, 1950 December 18 (Box 113, Folder 7)
    - HAUNT ME NOT by Leonard St. Clair, 1952 August 17 (Box 113, Folder 8)
      Starring Deborah Kerr.
    - STRANGE VENGEANCE by Harold Jack Bloom, 1950 November 27 (Box 113, Folder 9)
    - STATEMENT IN FULL by Maurice Zimm, 1952 August 19 (Box 113, Folder 10)
      Starring Marilyn Monroe.
    - DEATH IS A RIGHT HOOK by Antony Ellis and Anthony Barrett, 1951 May 7 (Box 113, Folder 11)
    - KILLER'S MOON by Harold Swanton, 1951 October 11 (Box 113, Folder 12)
    - DEATH IS A RIGHT HOOK by Antony Ellis and Anthony Barrett, 1952 March 23 (Box 113, Folder 13)
    - DEATH IS A RIGHT HOOK by Antony Ellis and Anthony Barrett, undated (Box 113, Folder 14)
    - THE WORD by Arch Oboler, 1952 November 30 (Box 113, Folder 15)
    - MEMORY OF THE FUTURE by Leonard St. Clair, 1952 December 7 (Box 113, Folder 16)
      Starring Ronald Reagan.
    - UNTIL MIDNIGHT by Leonard St. Clair, 1951 August 30 (Box 113, Folder 17)
    - BLIND FLIGHT by Harold Swanton (Box 113, Folder 18)
    - THE WRONG PAIR OF SHOES by David Chantler, 1952 March 25 (Box 113, Folder 19)
    - DREAM JOB by Bud Lesser, undated (Box 113, Folder 20)
    - THE LONG SHOT by Harold Swanton, 1952 June 8 (Box 113, Folder 21)
      Starring David Niven.
    - LAST CHANCE by Anthony Barrett, 1952 September 21 (Box 113, Folder 22)
      Starring Charlton Heston.
    - THE GUN AND MISS GREENFIELD by Frank Burt, 1951 (Box 113, Folder 23)
  - The Hollywood Story
    - RICHARD DIX, 1953 October 23 (Box 111, Folder 6)
  - I Was a Communist for the FBI (Syndicated, 1952-1953)
    - Script, undated (Box 112, Folder 16)
    - A RIOT MADE TO ORDER by Carl Leo Gass, undated (Box 116a, Folder 12)
    - KANGAROO COURT by Lester and Gerard, undated (Box 116a, Folder 13)
    - THE RED RECORD by Mindret Lord, undated (Box 116a, Folder 14)
  - Inheritance (Syndicated, 1953-1954)
    - THE STORY OF A SOLDIER by Milt Kahn, 1954 June 12 (Box 111, Folder 12)
  - The Irene Dunne/Fred MacMurray Show: Bright Star (Syndicated, 1952-1953)
    - SHOW #45, undated (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - Jason and the Golden Fleece (CBS, 1952-1953)
    - SHOW B, undated (Box 116, Folder 25)
    - PROGRAM #33 by Cleve Herman and Herb Ellis, 1953 June 11 (Box 116, Folder 26)
    - PROGRAM #33 by Cleve Herman and Herb Ellis, 1953 June 5 (Box 116, Folder 27)
    - PROGRAM #29 by Cleve Herman and Herb Ellis, 1953 May 31 (Box 116, Folder 29)
    - PROGRAM NO. 21 by Cleve Herman and Herb Ellis, 1953 March 27 (Box 116, Folder 29)
    - PROGRAM NUMBER 16 by Cleve Herman and Herb Ellis, 1953 February 12 (Box 116, Folder 30)
  - Let George Do It (Don Lee-Mutual, 1946-1954)
    - THE VIOLENT VAN PATTENS by Victor and Gillis, 1952 June 2 (Box 114, Folder 8)
    - BIG BROTHER by David Victor and Jackson Gillis, 1951 May 21 (Box 114, Folder 9)
    - SABOTAGE by Lloyd London, 1952 July 7 (Box 114, Folder 10)
    - DESTINATION - DANGER! by Don Clark, 1951 November 19 (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - The Lineup (CBS, 1953-1954)
    - THE ABEYANT ABNEGATED ALIBI CASE by Morton Fine and David Friedkin, 1951 September 19 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Script, 1950 July 13 (Box 102, Folder 16)
    - THE GUIDED GANG CASE by Charles Israel and Blake Edwards, 1952 June 26 (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - THE POKER PARTY KILLINGS by E. Jack Neuman, 1952 October 1 (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - THE BE-BOP BANDITS BUNGLING BANG-BANG by William J. Ratcliff, 1952 November 5 (Box 102, Folder 19)
  - Lux Radio Theatre (1935-1955)
    - DEADLINE -- USA, undated (Box 102a, Folder 21)
    - CAPTAIN CAREY, USA, undated (Box 111, Folder 11)
    - SKIRTS AHOY, undated (Box 111, Folder 15)
    - CAPTAIN HORATIO HORNBLOWER, undated (Box 116a, Folder 9)
    - UNION STATION, undated (Box 116a, Folder 10)
    - SHOW BOAT, undated (Box 116a, Folder 11)
      This is an adaptation of the 1951 film version.
  - The Lux Summer Theatre (CBS, 1953)
    - THE AFFAIRS OF SUSAN title page, 1953 August 24 (Box 112, Folder 15)
  - The Man Called X (CBS/NBC, 1944-1952)
    - HOT SPOT, 1951 (Box 109a, Folder 11)
    - THE PLOWSHARES OF CIENTO by Sidney Marshall, 1952 April 15 (Box 109a, Folder 13)
    - THE BAMBOO CURTAIN, 1951 October 5 (Box 109a, Folder 14)
    - DEATH ALSO HAS WINGS, 1951 September 21 (Box 109a, Folder 15)
    - MURDER BY INVITATION, 1951 (Box 109a, Folder 17)
    - NO GREATER WEAPON, 1952 (Box 109a, Folder 18)
    - DEATH DIVIDED BY FIVE, undated (Box 109a, Folder 19)
    - THE MONTE CARLO GAMBLE, 1951 (Box 109a, Folder 20)
    - THE LAST ISLAND by Sidney Marshall, 1951 May 25 (Box 109a, Folder 21)
    - Script, undated (Box 109a, Folder 22)
  - The Man from Homicide (ABC, 1951)
    - NO. 14, 1951 September 20 (Box 102a, Folder 20)
  - Marian Theater
    - THE NIGHTCALL by Robert Hugh O'Sullivan, 1957 March 20 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Martin Kane, Private Eye (Mutual, 1949-1951; NBC, 1951-1952)
    - SCRIPT #99, 1951 July 1 (Box 106, Folder 15)
    - SCRIPT #103 script pages, 1951 July 29 (Box 106, Folder 16)
  - Meet Corliss Archer (1943-1956)
    - THE DANCE by Lee Karson, 1953 January 23 (Box 111, Folder 18)
  - The Modern Adventures of Casanova (Mutual, 1952)
    - PROGRAM #14 by Harold Swanton, undated (Box 106, Folder 12)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Blandings (NBC, 1951)
    - SHOW #18 by Mort Lachman and Chuck Stewart, undated (Box 106, Folder 19)
    - PROGRAM #17 by M. Winkle, 1951 May 10 (Box 106, Folder 25)
  - Mr. and Mrs. North (NBC/CBS, 1942-1954)
    - HOUSE OF HATE, 1953 September 29 (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Mr. District Attorney (NBC/ABC, 1939-1952)
    - CASE OF THE COUNTRY CLUB MURDER by Vic Whitman, undated (Box 106, Folder 20)
    - THE TELEPHONE TENANTS by Herb Purdum, undated (Box 106, Folder 21)
  - Mr. President (ABC, 1947-1953)
    - GEORGE WASHINGTON by Ira Marion, 1951 December 22 (Box 102a, Folder 18)
  - Night Beat (NBC, 1950-1952)
    - PROGRAM #48, 1951 June 12 (Box 102, Folder 20)
    - PROGRAM #61, 1951 September 30 (Box 102, Folder 21)
    - PROGRAM #84, 1952 March 14 (Box 102, Folder 22)
    - PROGRAM #103, undated (Box 102, Folder 23)
  - O'Hara (CBS, 1951 and 1956)
    - ASSIGNMENT: ASSASSINATION, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - RETURN OF SUN WAH KEE, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - THE HONEY BLONDE PIRATE, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - RED RUBIES FROM BURMA, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - INCIDENT AT BIAS BAY, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - INTERVIEW RAMON DELGADO, undated (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - THE WOMAN WHO HAD EVERYTHING by Irene Winston, 1956 May 27 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - CELESTIAL CELESTINE by William N. Robson, 1956 June 3 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - THE LEGEND by Tony Barrett, 1956 June 10 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - THE SET-UP by Tony Barrett, 1956 June 21 (Box 105, Folder 10)
  - One Man's Family (NBC, 1932-1959)
    - CHAPTER 34 BOOK 100, 1953 February 19 (Box 111, Folder 7)
  - Operation Underground
    - RUSSIAN AGENT, undated (Box 102a, Folder 14)
    - THE VOICE OF THE BITTER WIND, 1952 April 12 (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Richard Diamond, Private Detective (NBC/ABC/CBS, 1949-1953)
    - Script by Blake Edwards, 1951 December 22 (Box 110, Folder 18)
    - DANNY REVERE CASE by Gil Doud, 1952 June 20 (Box 110, Folder 19)
    - THE BARRIO CASE, 1951 April 18 (Box 110, Folder 20)
    - THE FIGHT FIX, 1951 April 4 (Box 110, Folder 21)
    - THE CARNIVAL, 1951 March 21 (Box 110, Folder 23)
    - THE HANK BURTON CASE by Dick Carr, 1952 March 6 (Box 110, Folder 24)
  - Rocky Fortune (NBC, 1953-1954)
    - SITTING DUCK FOR DEATH script pages by George Lefferts, 1954 (Box 102a, Folder 14)
    - DEATH TAKES A CRUISE by George Lefferts, 1953 October 23 (Box 106, Folder 1)
  - Rocky Jordan (CBS, 1948-1951)
    - VALLEY OF THE DEAD, 1951 July 12 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - THE MAROUF PLAN, 1951 July 19 (Box 106, Folder 3)
  - Romance (CBS, 1943-1957)
    - SAN FRANCISCO INCIDENT by John Dawson, 1956 February 1 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      Music by Jerry Goldsmith.
    - CAPTAIN HUCKABEE'S BEARD by Walter Brown Newman, 1953 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - MISSION by William N. Robson from a story by William Kenneally, 1955 October 12 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - HOUR OF TRUTH by E. Jack Neuman, 1953 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - MADAME 44 by John Meston from a story by Michael Foster, 1952 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - SEMI-PRIVATE EYE by Kathleen Hite, 1955 January 29 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - THE LONG WAY HOME by Leonard St. Clair, 1954 July 23 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - THE BACHELOR by E. Jack Neuman, 1952 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - THE GUITAR by Tony Barrett, 1956 December 4 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - THE GUITAR treatment by Tony Barrett, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 10)
  - The Roy Rogers Radio Show (Mutual/NBC, 1944-1955)
    - GOLDEN EARRINGS by Ralph Rose and Charles Smith, undated (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - MARDI GRAS by Ralph Rose and Charles Smith, undated (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - FAR AWAY PLACES by Ralph Rose and Charles Smith, undated (Box 107, Folder 7)
    - RIVER OF NO RETURN by Ralph Rose and Charles Smith, undated (Box 107, Folder 8)
  - The Saint (NBC, 1950-1951)
    - THE BIG SWINDLE by Michael Cramoy, 1951 February 9 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - THE MISSING WITNESS CASE, 1951 September 18 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - Screen Directors' Playhouse (NBC, 1949-1951)